Guide to the Stanford University, Center for African Studies, Records SC0832
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Accession ARCH-2006-217
  - Audiovisual materials
    - Audiocassettes
      - Conferences:
        - Joint Center Conference 2000 (Box 24)
        - April 1991 "African Identities" Conference:
          - Keynote Speaker: Gibson Kaman Kuria (Box 24)
          - Values and Symbols in Nigerian Culture (Box 24)
          - South Africa (Box 24)
          - Political Ideas and Institutions (Box 24)
          - Samoff Panel: O. Macalon (Box 24)
        - 1989 Conference:
          - Colloquium on World Bank Strategy for Africa (Box 24)
          - South Africa (Box 24)
          - Literary and Political Perspectives on Social Conflict (Box 24)
          - Political Economy (Box 24)
          - African-Chinese Relations (Box 24)
          - International Dimensions of Conflict (Box 24)
          - Roundtable (Box 24)
          - Keynote Address Oyeleye Oyediran (Box 24)
      - SAFI:
        - 11/3/92, 3/7/94, 3/4/98, 6/8/98, 2/12/01, 1992-2001 (Box 24)
      - CAS Meetings:
        - 11/16/92, 5/17/93, 9/27/93, 12/10/93, 1/24/94, 3/7/94, 4/4/94, 6/6/94, 10/10/94, 11/7/94, 4/3/95, 6/5/95, 10/2/95, 12/11/95, 2/5/96, 3/4/96, 4/15/96, 6/3/96, 2/8/97, 1/12/98, 2/2/98, 4/6/98, 5/4/98, 6/8/98, 11/2/98, 12/7/98, 2/1/99, 1/10/00, 2/7/00, 3/6/00, 4/3/00, 5/8/00, 6/5/00, 10/2/00, 11/6/00, 12/4/00, 1/22/01, 2/12/01, 3/2/01, 4/9/01, 5/7/01, 10/6/01, 12/3/01, 1/14/02, 4/15/02, 6/10/02, 11/11/02, 12/16/02, 1/13/03, 4/21/03, 6/2/03, 11/3/03, 1/20/04, 4/5/04, 11/01/04, 12/6/04, 1/10/05, 2/7/05, 3/7/05, 4/4/05, 5/05, 6/6/05, 5/5/?, 11/8/?, 9/30/?, 1/13/?, 1992-2005 (Box 24)
      - Random:
        - Moose Talk 3/16/94 (Box 24)
        - Translation 9/17/83 (Box 24)
        - Bill Evans (Box 24)
        - South Africa Education Project 6/10/94 (Box 24)
        - West African Music (Box 24)
        - Helmut Angula, Sat., April 22, 1989 (Box 24)
        - The Angola/Namibia Peace Accords (Box 24)
  - Computer files
    - Box A:
      - Appendix in Proposal of Faculty CVs (Box 25)
      - Merge Disk C&D Trial (Box 25)
      - Courses PFS used to make the Course Booklet 88-89 (Box 25)
      - Copy C&D 88 (Box 25)
      - Main Student File b: Student 9/88 (Box 25)
      - B: Enroll 87-88, Course Enrollments, B: Courses 87 (Box 25)
      - WP, B: Cournums (86-87) 7/8/87 (Box 25)
      - B: Faculty Back-up Copy 10/86 (Box 25)
      - PFS B: Faculty "Copy" (Box 25)
      - PFS Events 86-87 Copy (Box 25)
      - WP Cournums (86-87) back-up copy (Box 25)
      - PFS Faculty 86 Copy (Box 25)
      - B: Enroll 87, Course Enrollments 87-88, 9/10/87 copy (Box 25)
      - B: Student info 7/23/87 (Box 25)
    - Box B:
      - FLAS Budget African Studies (Box 25)
      - Budget Files 6/11/87 (Box 25)
      - Budgets (Box 25)
      - Lotus Address Macros (Louise) (Box 25)
      - Backup 87-88 Budget (Box 25)
      - View of 123: Backup (Box 25)
      - 123 Install Library backup (Box 25)
      - 123 Utility Disk backup (Box 25)
      - News 3.90 (Box 25)
      - 5.0 news 4.89, news 5.89, news 1.90, news 2.9 (Box 25)
      - Newsletter 89-90 (4.2) (Box 25)
      - Newsletter 88-89 (Box 25)
      - Copy newsletter 86/87 and 87/88 (Box 25)
      - Newsletters 86/87, 87/88 11/6/86 (Box 25)
      - Proposal 88, UCB copy (Box 25)
      - AFPRO88 (Box 25)
      - DOS 2.1 Wordstar mailmerge for the NEC Spinwriter (Box 25)
      - Faculty CV 8/24/87 (Box 25)
    - Box C: Copies of Working Files 8/31/87
      - General Office #5 5/11/88, main files for C&D backup (Box 25)
      - General Office #3 5/28/87 (Box 25)
      - Bob #2 (Box 25)
      - Bob's Disc (Box 25)
      - Pam's Misc 8/85 (Box 25)
      - Reporter backup (Box 25)
      - General office memos, letters, CAS minutes #1, 11/86 (Box 25)
      - Newsletters 86-87 backup (Box 25)
      - Cathy 1 WS (Box 25)
      - General Office #3 Memos, hrs, CAS minutes, budgets 5/28/87 (Box 25)
      - General Office memos, letters, CAS minutes #2 2/9/87 (Box 25)
      - General Office #2 5/28/87 (Box 25)
      - Cathy 2 9/10/86 (Box 25)
      - General Office #3 memos, hrs, CAS minutes, budgets 4/17/87 (Box 25)
      - General office #4 memos, letters, CAS minutes 9/28/87 (Box 25)
      - General office #4 memos, hrs, CAS minutes (Box 25)
      - Forms 8/20/86 (Box 25)
    - Box D:
      - Proposal 1988 11/4/88 (Box 25)
      - AF Studies Proposal 91 (Box 25)
      - Enroll 89, courses and enrollments (Box 25)
      - African Studies budget Carole Miller (Box 25)
      - B: CV87A (and a copy) (Box 25)
      - African Studies CV (Box 25)
      - 87-88 Faculty, CVS copy, 12/6/84 (Box 25)
      - Proposal files on hard disk #2 backup (Box 25)
      - African Studies CVs 12/6/84 (Box 25)
      - Final Version Proposal 1/27/88 (Box 25)
      - Proposal 88-91, course list appendix (Box 25)
      - Samson Communications w/IBM (Box 25)
      - Cathy 1 backup (Box 25)
      - Cathy2 9/10/86 backup (Box 25)
    - Box E:
      - Proposal Complete version (and backup) (Box 25)
      - Proposal disk M Individual files (2 discs) (Box 25)
      - Proposal disk N individual files (2 discs) (Box 25)
      - Proposal text 10/31/86 copy 1 (Box 25)
      - Proposal B:propl-4, B:propl5-7 copy (Box 25)
      - B: Proposal 87-88 copy of 11/18/86 (Box 25)
      - DOE memos, data collection, 86-87 courses (Box 25)
      - 86-87 proposal copy WS 11/4/86 (Box 25)
      - Proposal 87-88 (Box 25)
      - Wp system disk 10/86 (Box 25)
      - Proposal 86-87 WS (Box 25)
    - Box F:
      - African PFS student info copy (Box 25)
      - B: enroll (85/86 courses) backup (Box 25)
      - Cournums backup (Box 25)
      - 85-86 events PFS copy (Box 25)
      - B: Student 5/85 student info (prime) backup (Box 25)
      - B: enroll copy (Box 25)
      - B: student copy (Box 25)
      - African Studies mailing list (Box 25)
      - 84-85 AF Studies events (Box 25)
      - PFS Africa events, AS Awards (Box 25)
      - Student info backup (Box 25)
      - 84-85 AF Studies events copy (Box 25)
      - B: Reporter 12/19/86 (and copy) (Box 25)
      - Proposal Sections for the Reporter (Box 25)
    - Box G:
      - African Studies DOS 2.1 WS 11/4/86 (Box 25)
      - Budget (Box 25)
      - Conference 93 (Box 25)
      - Faculty 90, ½ page CVs for proposal (Box 25)
      - Pfs\pf.ovl (Box 25)
      - Pfs\mail88, \pf.exe, \pf.pri, \pf.pif (Box 25)
      - Samson\*.* (Box 25)
      - Wintcp\telnet.exe à end (Box 25)
      - Wintcp\*.* (through FTP.exe) (Box 25)
      - Wp forms and instruct. 9/15/87 (and copy) (Box 25)
      - General office #6 hrs, memos, CAS minutes 1/16/89 (Box 25)
      - General office #5 5/11/88 (Box 25)
      - CAS faculty disk, faculty ques. (Box 25)
      - African Studies events, other campus prog. 86/87, 87/88. 88/89 (Box 25)
      - Faculty 86, 3 yr proposal 88-91 (Box 25)
      - PFS faculty 84/85, 85/86 11/3/86 (Box 25)
      - May 11 Conference Proposal (and copy) (Box 25)
      - FLAS budget, operation 84/85, budget (prop. For 86-87) (Box 25)
      - 86-87 budgets (lotus), overview (Box 25)
    - Box H:
      - PFS files 85-86 (w/backups) PFS files 86-87 backups only (Box 25)
      - B: mail update 9/88 copy (Box 25)
      - PFS student info 9/88 copy (Box 25)
      - B: courses 87 master, B: course31 daily backups (Box 25)
      - Course nos. B: coursenums backup 11/3/86 (Box 25)
      - PFS file and report (master disk for AS) w/o Dos program 11/3/86 (Box 25)
      - PFS course enrollments 85/86 11/3/86 (and copy) (Box 25)
      - PFS events 85/86 (Box 25)
      - PFS events 85-86 11/3/86 (Box 25)
      - PFS enroll copy 11/86 (Box 25)
      - Enroll, course enrollments 85-86 (Box 25)
      - Course numbers African Studies (Box 25)
      - African Studies faculty CV master copy (Box 25)
      - Course numbers African Studies cournums (Box 25)
    - Box I:
      - Ling-Staff (Box 25)
      - Title VI Courses, Appendix, Budget 94-95 (Box 25)
      - Allcours.89, allcours.90, allcours.91, coursmem.91, allcours.92 (Box 25)
      - 94-95 Title VI proposal faculty appendix (Box 25)
      - 92-93 Expenditure (Box 25)
      - Wperf. "Marianne" Dir. Mearsmem.94 (Box 25)